<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<?xml-model href="flowers.sch" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<topic id="growing_flowers">
  <title>Growing <b>Flowers</b></title>
  <body>
    <section>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <p>With just a little bit of care and preparation, any flower garden can be a vibrantly
        colored environment. Flowers can be selected for specific blooming seasons, colors and
        shapes. Both annual and perennial flower gardens can be planted depending on climate and
        specific needs.</p>
      <p>Read more about growing flowers here:</p>
      <ul id="read_more_list">
        <li><xref href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flower_garden" format="html" scope="external"
            >Flower garden</xref>;</li>
        <li><xref href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Raised-bed_gardening" format="html"
            scope="external">Raised-bed gardening</xref>;</li>
        <li><xref href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Compost" scope="external">Compost</xref></li>
      </ul>
      <p>Most of the information was taken from <xref href="www.wikipedia.org/" format="html"
          scope="external"/>, the free encyclopedia.</p>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title>Care and Preparation</title>
      <p>When caring for your flower garden you want to feed your plants properly, control pests and
        weeds. Good soil is a must to successful gardening, landscaping, and healthy flowers. You
        have to balance the soil structure with nutrients and regulate the pH to cover your plants'
        needs. And above all, remember that many flower gardens fail because they just don't get
        enough of your attention.</p>
      <table frame="all" rowsep="1" colsep="1" id="flowers_table">
        <title>Flowers</title>
        <tgroup cols="3">
          <colspec colname="c1" colnum="1" colwidth="1.0*"/>
          <colspec colname="c2" colnum="2" colwidth="1.0*"/>
          <colspec colname="c3" colnum="3" colwidth="1.0*"/>
          <thead>
            <row>
              <entry>Flower</entry>
              <entry>Type</entry>
            </row>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <row>
              <entry>Chrysanthemum</entry>
              <entry>perennial</entry>
              <entry>well drained</entry>
            </row>
            <row>
              <entry>Gardenia</entry>
              <entry>perennial</entry>
            </row>
            <row>
              <entry>Gerbera</entry>
              <entry>annual</entry>
              <entry>sandy, well-drained</entry>
            </row>
            <row>
              <entry>Iris</entry>
            </row>
          </tbody>
        </tgroup>
      </table>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title>Flowers by Season</title>
      <p>The various climatic changes that occur in cyclic pattern are termed as 'Seasons'. There
        are four general seasons occurring on Earth - Spring, Summer, Autumn and Winter.</p>
      <ol id="flowers_by_season_list">
        <li>Spring Flowers<ul id="spring_flowers_list">
            <li>
              <p>Iris - is a genus of between 200-300 species of flowering plants with showy
                flowers.</p>
              <ul id="spring_flowers_others_list">
                <li>
                  <p>Irises are extensively grown as ornamental plants in home and botanical
                    gardens.</p>
                </li>
                <li>
                  <p>Some rhizomes are traded as orris root and are used in perfume and medicine,
                    though more common in ancient times than today.</p>
                </li>
              </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
              <p>Snowdrop - is the common name for members of the genus Galanthus, a small genus of
                about 20 species in the family Amaryllidaceae.</p>
            </li>
          </ul></li>
        <li>Summer Flowers<ul id="summer_flowers_list">
            <li>
              <p>Gardenia - is a genus of about 250 species of flowering plants in the coffee
                family, Rubiaceae, native to the tropical and subtropical regions of Africa,
                southern Asia, Australasia and Oceania.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
              <p>Lilac - is a genus of about 20–25 species of flowering plants in the olive family
                (Oleaceae), native to Europe and Asia.</p>
            </li>
          </ul></li>
        <li>Autumn Flowers<ul id="autumn_flowers_list">
            <li>
              <p>Chrysanthemum - often called 'mums', are a genus (Chrysanthemum) of about 30
                species of perennial flowering plants in the family Asteraceae, native to Asia and
                northeastern Europe.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
              <p>Salvia - is the largest genus of plants in the mint family, Lamiaceae, with
                approximately 900 species of shrubs, herbaceous perennials, and annuals. It is one
                of three genera commonly referred to as sage.</p>
            </li>
          </ul></li>
        <li>Winter Flowers<ul id="winter_flowers_list">
            <li>
              <p>Gerbera - is a genus of ornamental plants from the sunflower family (Asteraceae).
                It was named in honor of the German naturalist Traugott Gerber.</p>
            </li>
          </ul></li>
      </ol>
    </section>
  </body>
</topic>
